<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>CSIS — Analysis (custom RSS)</title><link>https://www.csis.org/analysis</link><description>Auto-generated RSS feed for CSIS Analysis pages.</description><lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 08:16:05 +0000</lastBuildDate><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>Jungle Thunder: A Multinational Approach to Improving U.S. Capabilities in Jungle Warfare</title><link>https://www.csis.org/analysis/jungle-thunder-multinational-approach-improving-us-capabilities-jungle-warfare</link><guid>https://www.csis.org/analysis/jungle-thunder-multinational-approach-improving-us-capabilities-jungle-warfare</guid><description>Senior Associate Wilder Alejandro Sánchez and Andre Carvalho assess the U.S. jungle warfare readiness and propose new mechanisms for cooperation between U.S. and Latin American forces to increase combat readiness.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 08:16:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Russia’s Intense Air Campaign in October</title><link>https://www.csis.org/analysis/russias-intense-air-campaign-october</link><guid>https://www.csis.org/analysis/russias-intense-air-campaign-october</guid><description>Russia's recent missile strikes indicate a transition in strategy and doctrine, where industrial capacity plays a growing role in determining battlefield dynamics. Massed salvos have given way to a more flexible strike schedule, necessitating an adaptive defensive strategy.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 08:16:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>How Important Is Blue Origin’s Second New Glenn Launch?</title><link>https://www.csis.org/analysis/how-important-blue-origins-second-new-glenn-launch</link><guid>https://www.csis.org/analysis/how-important-blue-origins-second-new-glenn-launch</guid><description>With the second launch of New Glenn, Blue Origin becomes only the second space operator in the world to conduct a vertical landing of an orbital-class booster. The Pentagon, NASA, and commercial customers are now counting on Blue Origin to deliver New Glenn at scale.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 08:16:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>USAID Youth Engagement: A Potential Generation Lost?</title><link>https://www.csis.org/analysis/usaid-youth-engagement-potential-generation-lost</link><guid>https://www.csis.org/analysis/usaid-youth-engagement-potential-generation-lost</guid><description>The halting of USAID’s youth programming represents a critical inflection point for U.S. development policy. The termination risks reversing gains in employment, social cohesion, and civic participation that underpin economic and democratic resilience.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 08:16:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>A Complex Legacy: U.S. Global Food Security Assistance, 2008–Present</title><link>https://www.csis.org/analysis/complex-legacy-us-global-food-security-assistance-2008-present</link><guid>https://www.csis.org/analysis/complex-legacy-us-global-food-security-assistance-2008-present</guid><description>Among U.S. global development programs paused or terminated in 2025 are those that aimed to improve global agriculture and nutrition. Through an interactive graphic, CSIS explores the history and status of U.S. government funding for eight of these programs.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 08:16:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Watered Down: A Weakened Global Water Strategy</title><link>https://www.csis.org/analysis/watered-down-weakened-global-water-strategy</link><guid>https://www.csis.org/analysis/watered-down-weakened-global-water-strategy</guid><description>The US Global Water Strategy reflects longstanding bipartisan commitments to promote safe water services in partner nations. The Trump administration’s radical reductions to foreign aid imperil these goals, making vulnerable populations weaker, poorer, and less secure.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 08:16:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>How U.S. Democracy, Human Rights, and Governance Cuts Could Undermine Global Development Gains</title><link>https://www.csis.org/analysis/how-us-democracy-human-rights-and-governance-cuts-could-undermine-global-development-gains</link><guid>https://www.csis.org/analysis/how-us-democracy-human-rights-and-governance-cuts-could-undermine-global-development-gains</guid><description>While the Trump administration dismantled much of the foreign assistance ecosystem, democracy, human rights, and governance programming and approaches were particularly targeted. Any development work without these efforts is unsustainable.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 08:16:05 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>How Mexico’s Costly Spectrum Undermines Its Digital Future</title><link>https://www.csis.org/analysis/how-mexicos-costly-spectrum-undermines-its-digital-future</link><guid>https://www.csis.org/analysis/how-mexicos-costly-spectrum-undermines-its-digital-future</guid><description>CSIS Americas experts assess how Mexico's high fees for wireless spectrum undermine its competitiveness ahead of the 2026 USMCA Joint Review.</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Nov 2025 08:16:05 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>