<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>CSIS — Analysis (custom RSS)</title><link>https://www.csis.org/analysis</link><description>Auto-generated RSS feed for CSIS Analysis pages.</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 14:13:57 +0000</lastBuildDate><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>China’s Trade Bullying Can’t Stand Up to a United Front</title><link>https://www.washingtonpost.com/opinions/2025/10/27/china-trade-rare-earth-minerals-leverage/</link><guid>https://www.washingtonpost.com/opinions/2025/10/27/china-trade-rare-earth-minerals-leverage/</guid><description>"Trade interdependence is a two-way street, and China is not the only one with leverage,” write CSIS’s Victor Cha and Andy Lim with Ellen Kim in The Washington Post.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 14:13:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Aligning APEC Beyond Trade Turmoil</title><link>https://www.csis.org/analysis/aligning-apec-beyond-trade-turmoil</link><guid>https://www.csis.org/analysis/aligning-apec-beyond-trade-turmoil</guid><description>On October 31, Trump, Xi, and other regional leaders will convene for the APEC Summit. Amid renewed U.S.-China trade tensions, supply chain disruptions, and growing geoeconomic fragmentation, how can the region chart a path toward a more resilient future?</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 14:13:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>APEC’s Opportunity to Catalyze Mineral Security Cooperation</title><link>https://www.csis.org/analysis/apecs-opportunity-catalyze-mineral-security-cooperation</link><guid>https://www.csis.org/analysis/apecs-opportunity-catalyze-mineral-security-cooperation</guid><description>The Asia-Pacific Economic Cooperation summit in South Korea next week offers an opportunity for the United States and its partners and allies to make serious progress on securing critical minerals supply chains.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 14:13:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>U.S. Carrier to the Caribbean: A Step Closer to War</title><link>https://www.csis.org/analysis/us-carrier-caribbean-step-closer-war</link><guid>https://www.csis.org/analysis/us-carrier-caribbean-step-closer-war</guid><description>Moving a carrier strike group is highly significant. U.S. forces are increasingly well positioned to conduct an air campaign against either the cartels or Venezuela—but don't yet have the combat power for a ground invasion.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 14:13:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Previewing President Trump’s Asia Visit</title><link>https://www.csis.org/analysis/press-briefing-previewing-president-trumps-asia-visit</link><guid>https://www.csis.org/analysis/press-briefing-previewing-president-trumps-asia-visit</guid><description>The Center for Strategic and International Studies (CSIS) hosted a call-in press briefing to preview President Trump's upcoming visit to Asia.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 14:13:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Pentagon Announces a New Counternarcotics Task Force in the Caribbean</title><link>https://www.csis.org/analysis/pentagon-announces-new-counternarcotics-task-force-caribbean</link><guid>https://www.csis.org/analysis/pentagon-announces-new-counternarcotics-task-force-caribbean</guid><description>CSIS Americas Program experts explain the significance of the Department of Defense’s establishment of a new Counternarcotics Task Force and consider how this reflects the Trump administration’s national security priorities.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 14:13:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Does the Golden Dome Create Strategic Instability or an Opportunity with China and Russia?</title><link>https://www.csis.org/analysis/does-golden-dome-create-strategic-instability-or-opportunity-china-and-russia</link><guid>https://www.csis.org/analysis/does-golden-dome-create-strategic-instability-or-opportunity-china-and-russia</guid><description>Rather than erode strategic stability, the Golden Dome will provide the United States a valuable security edge, a new tool for strategic deterrence, and a path to preserve peace.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 14:13:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>European Union’s Newfound Pragmatism Focuses on Emission Rules: Will It Appease Doha and Washington?</title><link>https://www.csis.org/analysis/european-unions-newfound-pragmatism-focuses-emission-rules-will-it-appease-doha-and</link><guid>https://www.csis.org/analysis/european-unions-newfound-pragmatism-focuses-emission-rules-will-it-appease-doha-and</guid><description>Europe is adopting key environmental measures with extraterritorial reach. For the first time, these rules could directly impact the business of the world’s largest gas and LNG producers, notably QatarEnergy and multiple U.S. companies.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 14:13:57 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>The U.S. Coast Guard and the Future of Maritime Cybersecurity</title><link>https://www.csis.org/analysis/us-coast-guard-and-future-maritime-cybersecurity</link><guid>https://www.csis.org/analysis/us-coast-guard-and-future-maritime-cybersecurity</guid><description>With nearly $25 billion in the One Big Beautiful Bill Act, a deep bench of cyber executive leaders, and recently expanded cyber authorities, the Coast Guard is poised to make generational improvements in maritime cybersecurity while bolstering its own cyber workforce.</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 14:13:57 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>