<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>CSIS — Analysis (custom RSS)</title><link>https://www.csis.org/analysis</link><description>Auto-generated RSS feed for CSIS Analysis pages.</description><lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 07:13:07 +0000</lastBuildDate><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>European Union’s Newfound Pragmatism Focuses on Emission Rules: Will It Appease Doha and Washington?</title><link>https://www.csis.org/analysis/european-unions-newfound-pragmatism-focuses-emission-rules-will-it-appease-doha-and</link><guid>https://www.csis.org/analysis/european-unions-newfound-pragmatism-focuses-emission-rules-will-it-appease-doha-and</guid><description>Europe is adopting key environmental measures with extraterritorial reach. For the first time, these rules could directly impact the business of the world’s largest gas and LNG producers, notably QatarEnergy and multiple U.S. companies.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 07:13:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>The U.S. Coast Guard and the Future of Maritime Cybersecurity</title><link>https://www.csis.org/analysis/us-coast-guard-and-future-maritime-cybersecurity</link><guid>https://www.csis.org/analysis/us-coast-guard-and-future-maritime-cybersecurity</guid><description>With nearly $25 billion in the One Big Beautiful Bill Act, a deep bench of cyber executive leaders, and recently expanded cyber authorities, the Coast Guard is poised to make generational improvements in maritime cybersecurity while bolstering its own cyber workforce.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 07:13:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Pentagon Announces a New Counternarcotics Task Force in the Caribbean</title><link>https://www.csis.org/analysis/pentagon-announces-new-counternarcotics-task-force-caribbean</link><guid>https://www.csis.org/analysis/pentagon-announces-new-counternarcotics-task-force-caribbean</guid><description>CSIS Americas Program experts explain the significance of the Department of Defense’s establishment of a new Counternarcotics Task Force and consider how this reflects the Trump administration’s national security priorities.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 07:13:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Does the Golden Dome Create Strategic Instability or an Opportunity with China and Russia?</title><link>https://www.csis.org/analysis/does-golden-dome-create-strategic-instability-or-opportunity-china-and-russia</link><guid>https://www.csis.org/analysis/does-golden-dome-create-strategic-instability-or-opportunity-china-and-russia</guid><description>Rather than erode strategic stability, the Golden Dome will provide the United States a valuable security edge, a new tool for strategic deterrence, and a path to preserve peace.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 07:13:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>States Weekly: October 22, 2025</title><link>https://www.csis.org/analysis/states-weekly-october-22-2025</link><guid>https://www.csis.org/analysis/states-weekly-october-22-2025</guid><description>This edition of States Weekly covers October 22, 2025.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 07:13:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>False Choices: Balancing Democracy and Development in U.S. Africa Policy</title><link>https://www.csis.org/analysis/false-choices-balancing-democracy-and-development-us-africa-policy</link><guid>https://www.csis.org/analysis/false-choices-balancing-democracy-and-development-us-africa-policy</guid><description>The shift in U.S. foreign policy to prioritize commercial diplomacy over democracy support presents a false dichotomy. As African partners adjust to the U.S. retreat as an advocate for democracy, this approach risks long-term consequences for U.S.-Africa relations.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 07:13:07 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>When Crime Becomes Terror: Rethinking the FTO Designation</title><link>https://www.csis.org/analysis/when-crime-becomes-terror-rethinking-fto-designation</link><guid>https://www.csis.org/analysis/when-crime-becomes-terror-rethinking-fto-designation</guid><description>CSIS Americas Research Associate Rubi Bledsoe analyzes the recent designations of criminal organizations as FTOs by the Trump administration and discusses key similarities and differences between the groups.</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 07:13:07 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>