<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>CSIS — Analysis (custom RSS)</title><link>https://www.csis.org/analysis</link><description>Auto-generated RSS feed for CSIS Analysis pages.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 14:14:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>If the Pentagon Wants More Speed and Scale, It Should Be a Better Customer</title><link>https://www.csis.org/analysis/if-pentagon-wants-more-speed-and-scale-it-should-be-better-customer</link><guid>https://www.csis.org/analysis/if-pentagon-wants-more-speed-and-scale-it-should-be-better-customer</guid><description>As the Department of War modernizes its acquisition process to optimize speed and scale, it should also think about how the Pentagon can be a better customer. Industry has to have trust that the military will stick to its budget plans.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 14:14:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Trump’s Caribbean Campaign: The Data Behind the Developing Conflict</title><link>https://www.csis.org/analysis/trumps-caribbean-campaign-data-behind-developing-conflict</link><guid>https://www.csis.org/analysis/trumps-caribbean-campaign-data-behind-developing-conflict</guid><description>The United States and Venezuela teeter on the brink of war. Twelve charts and tables lay out where we are, how we got here, and how a conflict might play out.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 14:14:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Waiting for the Supremes Part II</title><link>https://www.csis.org/analysis/waiting-supremes-part-ii</link><guid>https://www.csis.org/analysis/waiting-supremes-part-ii</guid><description>This week, Bill Reinsch examines the significance of the Supreme Court hearing on President Trump’s use of the International Economic Emergency Powers Act, outlining the key legal arguments and assessing the potential outcomes.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 14:14:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Trade Deals and a New Chapter for American Nuclear?</title><link>https://www.csis.org/analysis/trade-deals-and-new-chapter-american-nuclear</link><guid>https://www.csis.org/analysis/trade-deals-and-new-chapter-american-nuclear</guid><description>A slew of recently announced trade deals and investment agreements could amount to the most ambitious U.S. government action to support nuclear energy in decades, but key questions remain.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 14:14:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Rhetoric vs. Reality: The Philippines, ASEAN, and the South China Sea</title><link>https://www.csis.org/analysis/rhetoric-vs-reality-philippines-asean-and-south-china-sea</link><guid>https://www.csis.org/analysis/rhetoric-vs-reality-philippines-asean-and-south-china-sea</guid><description>Manila’s expanding defense partnerships may reveal a pragmatic strategy beyond relying on ASEAN’s consensus-based diplomacy.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 14:14:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Avoiding Catastrophe: The Importance of Privacy when Leveraging AI and Machine Learning for Disaster Management</title><link>https://www.csis.org/analysis/avoiding-catastrophe-importance-privacy-when-leveraging-ai-and-machine-learning-disaster</link><guid>https://www.csis.org/analysis/avoiding-catastrophe-importance-privacy-when-leveraging-ai-and-machine-learning-disaster</guid><description>Leveraging data effectively reduces disaster harms – but the data must be used in a responsible way that prioritizes security and privacy.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 14:14:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Ryan Berg in Foreign Policy: Toppling Maduro Without Boots on the Ground</title><link>https://foreignpolicy.com/2025/11/06/maduro-regime-change-collapse-trump-venezuela/</link><guid>https://foreignpolicy.com/2025/11/06/maduro-regime-change-collapse-trump-venezuela/</guid><description>Americas Program Director argues that rather than a ground invasion aimed at regime change, the pressure campaign by the Trump administration may lead to regime collapse, an outcome that is worth pursuing.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 14:14:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>What’s Next for AGOA?</title><link>https://www.csis.org/analysis/whats-next-agoa</link><guid>https://www.csis.org/analysis/whats-next-agoa</guid><description>The African Growth and Opportunity Act, the flagship U.S. trade agreement with Africa, has expired. As Washington debates the bill’s future, its uneven track record offers lessons on how to effectively strengthen U.S.-Africa commercial engagement moving forward.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 14:14:45 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Who Controls the Wrench: The Debate Over the “Right to Repair”</title><link>https://www.csis.org/analysis/who-controls-wrench-debate-over-right-repair</link><guid>https://www.csis.org/analysis/who-controls-wrench-debate-over-right-repair</guid><description>It is often a challenge for the government to repair its own equipment because it lacks access to the intellectual property necessary for sustainment. But there are pros and cons to the government having the right to repair.</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2025 14:14:45 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>