<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>CSIS — Analysis (custom RSS)</title><link>https://www.csis.org/analysis</link><description>Auto-generated RSS feed for CSIS Analysis pages.</description><lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 03:32:34 +0000</lastBuildDate><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>States Weekly: October 22, 2025</title><link>https://www.csis.org/analysis/states-weekly-october-22-2025</link><guid>https://www.csis.org/analysis/states-weekly-october-22-2025</guid><description>This edition of States Weekly covers October 22, 2025.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 03:32:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>When a Trade War Becomes a Food Fight</title><link>https://www.csis.org/analysis/when-trade-war-becomes-food-fight</link><guid>https://www.csis.org/analysis/when-trade-war-becomes-food-fight</guid><description>The U.S. agricultural sector is caught in the crossfire of the U.S.-China trade war. As Washington and Beijing escalate tariffs and other retaliatory measures, U.S. farmers are scrambling to find new buyers just as Chinese consumers turn to alternative suppliers.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 03:32:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>False Choices: Balancing Democracy and Development in U.S. Africa Policy</title><link>https://www.csis.org/analysis/false-choices-balancing-democracy-and-development-us-africa-policy</link><guid>https://www.csis.org/analysis/false-choices-balancing-democracy-and-development-us-africa-policy</guid><description>The shift in U.S. foreign policy to prioritize commercial diplomacy over democracy support presents a false dichotomy. As African partners adjust to the U.S. retreat as an advocate for democracy, this approach risks long-term consequences for U.S.-Africa relations.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 03:32:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>When Crime Becomes Terror: Rethinking the FTO Designation</title><link>https://www.csis.org/analysis/when-crime-becomes-terror-rethinking-fto-designation</link><guid>https://www.csis.org/analysis/when-crime-becomes-terror-rethinking-fto-designation</guid><description>CSIS Americas Research Associate Rubi Bledsoe analyzes the recent designations of criminal organizations as FTOs by the Trump administration and discusses key similarities and differences between the groups.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 03:32:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Ryan Berg in the Hoover Institution: Hemispheric Defense Is Back</title><link>https://www.hoover.org/research/hemispheric-defense-back</link><guid>https://www.hoover.org/research/hemispheric-defense-back</guid><description>Americas Program Director Ryan C. Berg and Joseph Ledford discuss ways in which the United States can craft a hemispheric strategy with global effectiveness.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 03:32:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Unpacking Ukraine’s Future Cyber and Space Forces</title><link>https://www.csis.org/analysis/unpacking-ukraines-future-cyber-and-space-forces</link><guid>https://www.csis.org/analysis/unpacking-ukraines-future-cyber-and-space-forces</guid><description>This piece explores the key questions surrounding Ukraine's proposed Cyber and Space Forces and what they will mean for the future of warfighting.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 03:32:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Unpacking the U.S.-Australia Critical Minerals Framework Agreement</title><link>https://www.csis.org/analysis/unpacking-us-australia-critical-minerals-framework-agreement</link><guid>https://www.csis.org/analysis/unpacking-us-australia-critical-minerals-framework-agreement</guid><description>The new U.S.–Australia Critical Minerals Framework cements the alliance as a cornerstone of global minerals security, combining over billions of dollars in joint investments with expanded defense cooperation—and reframing minerals as strategic assets, not just commodities.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 03:32:34 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>What Goes Around Comes Around and Other Cliches</title><link>https://www.csis.org/analysis/what-goes-around-comes-around-and-other-cliches</link><guid>https://www.csis.org/analysis/what-goes-around-comes-around-and-other-cliches</guid><description>This week, Bill Reinsch argues that China’s recent export controls are a direct response to U.S. trade measures. Rather than reacting with outrage, he suggests that the United States should avoid hypocrisy and adopt a more consistent strategy to de-escalate the growing trade tensions.</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 03:32:34 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>