<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>CSIS — Analysis (custom RSS)</title><link>https://www.csis.org/analysis</link><description>Auto-generated RSS feed for CSIS Analysis pages.</description><lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 05:12:09 +0000</lastBuildDate><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>Ahead of APEC, Trump Signs Flurry of Bilateral Minerals Agreements on Asia Tour</title><link>https://www.csis.org/analysis/ahead-apec-trump-signs-flurry-bilateral-minerals-agreements-asia-tour</link><guid>https://www.csis.org/analysis/ahead-apec-trump-signs-flurry-bilateral-minerals-agreements-asia-tour</guid><description>Leading up to the Asia-Pacific Economic Cooperation (APEC) summit in South Korea, President Trump signed new bilateral minerals agreements between the United States and Australia, Japan, Malaysia, and Thailand, marking an escalation in minerals diversification efforts.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 05:12:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>The Gloves Are Still On: Why Washington’s Newest Oil Sanctions Won’t Be Enough to Pressure Putin</title><link>https://www.csis.org/analysis/gloves-are-still-why-washingtons-newest-oil-sanctions-wont-be-enough-pressure-putin</link><guid>https://www.csis.org/analysis/gloves-are-still-why-washingtons-newest-oil-sanctions-wont-be-enough-pressure-putin</guid><description>President Trump’s new sanctions program on top Russian oil companies is a step in the right direction, but not enough to change behaviors in Moscow. Workarounds and lax enforcement will keep the barrels on the market, leaving Putin with enough revenues to continue the war.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 05:12:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Six Months Since the U.S.-Ukraine Minerals Deal Was Signed—What Now?</title><link>https://www.csis.org/analysis/six-months-us-ukraine-minerals-deal-was-signed-what-now</link><guid>https://www.csis.org/analysis/six-months-us-ukraine-minerals-deal-was-signed-what-now</guid><description>Six months ago, the U.S. and Ukraine launched the Reconstruction Investment Fund, placing critical minerals at its core to advance Ukraine’s economic recovery and enhance U.S. minerals security. What progress has been made to date, and what key actions are still required?</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 05:12:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Can the United States Immediately Return to Nuclear Testing?</title><link>https://www.csis.org/analysis/can-united-states-immediately-return-nuclear-testing</link><guid>https://www.csis.org/analysis/can-united-states-immediately-return-nuclear-testing</guid><description>President Trump’s post raises technical questions about how and if the United States could “immediately” return to nuclear testing, and political considerations about the signaling behind nuclear testing and who would benefit most from a return to testing.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 05:12:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>AI Needs Its Complements: Investing in the Next Wave of Innovation</title><link>https://www.csis.org/analysis/ai-needs-its-complements-investing-next-wave-innovation</link><guid>https://www.csis.org/analysis/ai-needs-its-complements-investing-next-wave-innovation</guid><description>As the United States advances its AI investments, it must also back complementary technologies that boost capability and ease resource limits. Quantum computing can overcome key constraints, helping the nation sustain innovation and long-term technological leadership.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 05:12:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>U.S. Universities: Engines of Economic Growth</title><link>https://www.csis.org/analysis/us-universities-engines-economic-growth</link><guid>https://www.csis.org/analysis/us-universities-engines-economic-growth</guid><description>University research is a proven job creator, an engine of regional economic growth, and a generator of entirely new industries that also advance public health, improve wellbeing, and bolster national security.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 05:12:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>After Argentina’s Midterms, a New Chapter for U.S.-Argentina Relations</title><link>https://www.csis.org/analysis/after-argentinas-midterms-new-chapter-us-argentina-relations</link><guid>https://www.csis.org/analysis/after-argentinas-midterms-new-chapter-us-argentina-relations</guid><description>CSIS Americas associate fellow Henry Ziemer and Henry Large argue that U.S. support for Argentina may provide a template for how Washington can compete with China in Latin America.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 05:12:09 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>States Weekly: October 29, 2025</title><link>https://www.csis.org/analysis/states-weekly-october-29-2025</link><guid>https://www.csis.org/analysis/states-weekly-october-29-2025</guid><description>This edition of States Weekly covers October 29, 2025.</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 05:12:09 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>