<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>CSIS — Analysis (custom RSS)</title><link>https://www.csis.org/analysis</link><description>Auto-generated RSS feed for CSIS Analysis pages.</description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 18:18:13 +0000</lastBuildDate><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>Unpacking Ukraine’s Future Cyber and Space Forces</title><link>https://www.csis.org/analysis/unpacking-ukraines-future-cyber-and-space-forces</link><guid>https://www.csis.org/analysis/unpacking-ukraines-future-cyber-and-space-forces</guid><description>This piece explores the key questions surrounding Ukraine's proposed Cyber and Space Forces and what they will mean for the future of warfighting.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 18:18:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Unpacking the U.S.-Australia Critical Minerals Framework Agreement</title><link>https://www.csis.org/analysis/unpacking-us-australia-critical-minerals-framework-agreement</link><guid>https://www.csis.org/analysis/unpacking-us-australia-critical-minerals-framework-agreement</guid><description>The new U.S.–Australia Critical Minerals Framework cements the alliance as a cornerstone of global minerals security, combining over billions of dollars in joint investments with expanded defense cooperation—and reframing minerals as strategic assets, not just commodities.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 18:18:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>What Goes Around Comes Around and Other Cliches</title><link>https://www.csis.org/analysis/what-goes-around-comes-around-and-other-cliches</link><guid>https://www.csis.org/analysis/what-goes-around-comes-around-and-other-cliches</guid><description>This week, Bill Reinsch argues that China’s recent export controls are a direct response to U.S. trade measures. Rather than reacting with outrage, he suggests that the United States should avoid hypocrisy and adopt a more consistent strategy to de-escalate the growing trade tensions.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 18:18:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Will the Tomahawks Save Ukraine?</title><link>https://www.csis.org/analysis/will-tomahawks-save-ukraine</link><guid>https://www.csis.org/analysis/will-tomahawks-save-ukraine</guid><description>About a thousand Tomahawk missiles in the U.S. stockpile today are available for transfer to Ukraine. They could have a major impact on the war, but the Pacific theater needs and Russian opposition could disrupt any deal.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 18:18:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>What Could a Trump Peace Plan in Ukraine Look Like?</title><link>https://www.csis.org/analysis/what-could-trump-peace-plan-ukraine-look</link><guid>https://www.csis.org/analysis/what-could-trump-peace-plan-ukraine-look</guid><description>As Trump’s team pushes for a Ukraine peace deal amid new pressure on Russia, experts and AI models outline the most likely outcomes, from frozen frontlines to the economic and security terms shaping negotiations.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 18:18:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Caribbean Update: Fifth Suspected Drug Runner Destroyed</title><link>https://www.csis.org/analysis/caribbean-update-fifth-suspected-drug-runner-destroyed</link><guid>https://www.csis.org/analysis/caribbean-update-fifth-suspected-drug-runner-destroyed</guid><description>U.S. attacks on suspected drug boats have become routine. They will likely continue until the administration decides to return the counterdrug mission to law enforcement agencies or a tragic incident heightens domestic and regional opposition to U.S. operations.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 18:18:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>In Memoriam: Debbie Stroman</title><link>https://www.csis.org/analysis/memoriam-debbie-stroman</link><guid>https://www.csis.org/analysis/memoriam-debbie-stroman</guid><description>CSIS President and CEO John Hamre issued a statement on the passing of CSIS Human Resources Special Assistant Deborah D. Stroman.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 18:18:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Power Moves: How China’s Energy Investments Provide Durable Influence in South America</title><link>https://www.csis.org/analysis/power-moves-how-chinas-energy-investments-provide-durable-influence-south-america</link><guid>https://www.csis.org/analysis/power-moves-how-chinas-energy-investments-provide-durable-influence-south-america</guid><description>CSIS Americas Associate Fellow Henry Ziemer evaluates China's investments in energy generation and distribution infrastructure in South America.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 18:18:13 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>What to Expect from the Trump-Albanese White House Meeting</title><link>https://www.csis.org/analysis/what-expect-trump-albanese-white-house-meeting</link><guid>https://www.csis.org/analysis/what-expect-trump-albanese-white-house-meeting</guid><description>When Anthony Albanese meets Donald Trump at the White House today, the stakes will be high for the U.S.-Australia alliance as tariffs, AUKUS, and critical minerals top the agenda.</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 Oct 2025 18:18:13 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>