<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>CSIS — Analysis (custom RSS)</title><link>https://www.csis.org/analysis</link><description>Auto-generated RSS feed for CSIS Analysis pages.</description><lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 06:20:26 +0000</lastBuildDate><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>When Thought Becomes Data: The MIND Act and the Coming Debate Over Neurotechnology</title><link>https://www.csis.org/analysis/when-thought-becomes-data-mind-act-and-coming-debate-over-neurotechnology</link><guid>https://www.csis.org/analysis/when-thought-becomes-data-mind-act-and-coming-debate-over-neurotechnology</guid><description>As neurotechnologies advance from medical tools to consumer devices, the question of who controls neural data is becoming urgent. The proposed MIND Act represents Congress’s first attempt to regulate this emerging domain, raising complex questions about privacy, innovation, and national security.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 06:20:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Leveraging Latin America’s Embrace of the United States</title><link>https://www.csis.org/analysis/leveraging-latin-americas-embrace-united-states</link><guid>https://www.csis.org/analysis/leveraging-latin-americas-embrace-united-states</guid><description>Americas Program Senior Associate Evan Ellis argues that the widespread U.S.-friendly disposition of Latin America and the Caribbean creates unique opportunities for the United States in economic, security and other domains.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 06:20:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Russia’s Nuclear-Powered Burevestnik Missile: Implications for Missile Defense</title><link>https://www.csis.org/analysis/russias-nuclear-powered-burevestnik-missile-implications-missile-defense</link><guid>https://www.csis.org/analysis/russias-nuclear-powered-burevestnik-missile-implications-missile-defense</guid><description>Nuclear-powered cruise missiles are not a new idea—they’re just a bad idea. While Russia’s Burevestnik missile is grabbing headlines, it does not fundamentally change Russia’s ability to hold the U.S. homeland at risk or the strategic balance between the two states.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 06:20:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Ten Years of C5+1: U.S.–Central Asia Minerals Cooperation</title><link>https://www.csis.org/analysis/ten-years-c51-us-central-asia-minerals-cooperation</link><guid>https://www.csis.org/analysis/ten-years-c51-us-central-asia-minerals-cooperation</guid><description>Amid a changing donor landscape, the United States has an opportunity to realign and leverage its full range of financing tools to promote economic growth abroad while safeguarding its national security interests.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 06:20:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>How a New Generation of Business Heroes is Changing Narratives about Latin America</title><link>https://mexiconewsdaily.com/business/opinion-how-a-new-generation-of-business-heroes-is-changing-narratives-about-latin-america/</link><guid>https://mexiconewsdaily.com/business/opinion-how-a-new-generation-of-business-heroes-is-changing-narratives-about-latin-america/</guid><description>Latin American entrepreneurs have put the region on the map for big business—and improved millions of lives in the process, writes Mariana Campero in Mexico News Daily.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 06:20:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>CSIS Names Aalok Mehta Director of the Wadhwani AI Center</title><link>https://www.csis.org/news/csis-names-aalok-mehta-director-wadhwani-ai-center</link><guid>https://www.csis.org/news/csis-names-aalok-mehta-director-wadhwani-ai-center</guid><description>The Center for Strategic and International Studies (CSIS) today announced that Aalok Mehta has joined the Economic Security and Technology Department (EST) as director of the Wadhwani AI Center.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 06:20:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Africa’s HIV Response and Emerging Health Security Redesign</title><link>https://www.csis.org/analysis/africas-hiv-response-and-emerging-health-security-redesign</link><guid>https://www.csis.org/analysis/africas-hiv-response-and-emerging-health-security-redesign</guid><description>The U.S. government’s sudden retreat on foreign assistance has significantly altered health security efforts in Africa, of which HIV has been the dominant focus. A redesigned approach, one with new commitments and opportunities, has been forming.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 06:20:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Bullying Can Work, but It Has Its Limits</title><link>https://www.csis.org/analysis/bullying-can-work-it-has-its-limits</link><guid>https://www.csis.org/analysis/bullying-can-work-it-has-its-limits</guid><description>This week, Bill Reinsch examines President Trump’s trade agreements in Asia, accessing their implications for the U.S. economy, digital trade, and the global trading system.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 06:20:26 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>The Gloves Are Still On: Why Washington’s Newest Oil Sanctions Won’t Be Enough to Pressure Putin</title><link>https://www.csis.org/analysis/gloves-are-still-why-washingtons-newest-oil-sanctions-wont-be-enough-pressure-putin</link><guid>https://www.csis.org/analysis/gloves-are-still-why-washingtons-newest-oil-sanctions-wont-be-enough-pressure-putin</guid><description>President Trump’s new sanctions program on top Russian oil companies is a step in the right direction, but not enough to change behaviors in Moscow. Workarounds and lax enforcement will keep the barrels on the market, leaving Putin with enough revenues to continue the war.</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 06:20:26 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>