<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>CSIS — Analysis (custom RSS)</title><link>https://www.csis.org/analysis</link><description>Auto-generated RSS feed for CSIS Analysis pages.</description><lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 23:12:17 +0000</lastBuildDate><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>Africa’s HIV Response and Emerging Health Security Redesign</title><link>https://www.csis.org/analysis/africas-hiv-response-and-emerging-health-security-redesign</link><guid>https://www.csis.org/analysis/africas-hiv-response-and-emerging-health-security-redesign</guid><description>The U.S. government’s sudden retreat on foreign assistance has significantly altered health security efforts in Africa, of which HIV has been the dominant focus. A redesigned approach, one with new commitments and opportunities, has been forming.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 23:12:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Bullying Can Work, but It Has Its Limits</title><link>https://www.csis.org/analysis/bullying-can-work-it-has-its-limits</link><guid>https://www.csis.org/analysis/bullying-can-work-it-has-its-limits</guid><description>This week, Bill Reinsch examines President Trump’s trade agreements in Asia, accessing their implications for the U.S. economy, digital trade, and the global trading system.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 23:12:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>The Gloves Are Still On: Why Washington’s Newest Oil Sanctions Won’t Be Enough to Pressure Putin</title><link>https://www.csis.org/analysis/gloves-are-still-why-washingtons-newest-oil-sanctions-wont-be-enough-pressure-putin</link><guid>https://www.csis.org/analysis/gloves-are-still-why-washingtons-newest-oil-sanctions-wont-be-enough-pressure-putin</guid><description>President Trump’s new sanctions program on top Russian oil companies is a step in the right direction, but not enough to change behaviors in Moscow. Workarounds and lax enforcement will keep the barrels on the market, leaving Putin with enough revenues to continue the war.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 23:12:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Ahead of APEC, Trump Signs Flurry of Bilateral Minerals Agreements on Asia Tour</title><link>https://www.csis.org/analysis/ahead-apec-trump-signs-flurry-bilateral-minerals-agreements-asia-tour</link><guid>https://www.csis.org/analysis/ahead-apec-trump-signs-flurry-bilateral-minerals-agreements-asia-tour</guid><description>Leading up to the Asia-Pacific Economic Cooperation (APEC) summit in South Korea, President Trump signed new bilateral minerals agreements between the United States and Australia, Japan, Malaysia, and Thailand, marking an escalation in minerals diversification efforts.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 23:12:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Can the United States Immediately Return to Nuclear Testing?</title><link>https://www.csis.org/analysis/can-united-states-immediately-return-nuclear-testing</link><guid>https://www.csis.org/analysis/can-united-states-immediately-return-nuclear-testing</guid><description>President Trump’s post raises technical questions about how and if the United States could “immediately” return to nuclear testing, and political considerations about the signaling behind nuclear testing and who would benefit most from a return to testing.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 23:12:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>Six Months Since the U.S.-Ukraine Minerals Deal Was Signed—What Now?</title><link>https://www.csis.org/analysis/six-months-us-ukraine-minerals-deal-was-signed-what-now</link><guid>https://www.csis.org/analysis/six-months-us-ukraine-minerals-deal-was-signed-what-now</guid><description>Six months ago, the U.S. and Ukraine launched the Reconstruction Investment Fund, placing critical minerals at its core to advance Ukraine’s economic recovery and enhance U.S. minerals security. What progress has been made to date, and what key actions are still required?</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 23:12:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>U.S. Universities: Engines of Economic Growth</title><link>https://www.csis.org/analysis/us-universities-engines-economic-growth</link><guid>https://www.csis.org/analysis/us-universities-engines-economic-growth</guid><description>University research is a proven job creator, an engine of regional economic growth, and a generator of entirely new industries that also advance public health, improve wellbeing, and bolster national security.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 23:12:17 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>After Argentina’s Midterms, a New Chapter for U.S.-Argentina Relations</title><link>https://www.csis.org/analysis/after-argentinas-midterms-new-chapter-us-argentina-relations</link><guid>https://www.csis.org/analysis/after-argentinas-midterms-new-chapter-us-argentina-relations</guid><description>CSIS Americas associate fellow Henry Ziemer and Henry Large argue that U.S. support for Argentina may provide a template for how Washington can compete with China in Latin America.</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 23:12:17 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>